http://www.actuarialbookstore.com/privacy.aspx

Hello.  Sign In
Cart (0 items)
Toggle navigation
Home
Shop
Clearance CenterON SALECAS ExamsSOA Exam P / CAS Exam 1 SOA Exam FMSOA IFMCAS MAS-ICAS MAS-IICAS 5CAS 6CAS 7CAS 8CAS 9SOA ExamsSOA Exam P / CAS Exam 1 SOA Exam FMSOA IFMSOA LTAMSOA STAMSOA SRMSOA PASOA FAP (2020)SOA ERM- General Corporate ERM Extension SOA ERM- General Insurance Extension SOA ERM- Group & Health Extension SOA ERM- Individual Life & Annuities Extension SOA ERM- Investment Extension SOA ERM- Retirement Benefits ExtensionSOA CFE - Foundations of CFESOA CFE - Strategic Decision MakingSOA QFI - Quantitative Finance ExamSOA QFI - Portfolio ManagementSOA QFI - Investment Risk ManagementSOA ILA - Life Product ManagementSOA ILA - Life Financial Management: Canada ExamSOA ILA - Life Financial Management: US ExamSOA ILA - Life ALM & ModelingSOA RET - Funding and Regulation CANADA ExamSOA RET - Design & Accounting CANADASOA RET - Design & Accounting USSOA RET - Retirement Plan Investment & Risk MgmtSOA GH - Design & PricingSOA GH - DP (A) + FV (A)SOA GH - DP (C) + FV-US (C) SOA GH - Finance & Valuation CANADASOA GH - Finance & Valuation USSOA GH - Group Health SpecialtySOA GI - Introduction to General InsuranceSOA GI - Intro to Ratemaking & Reserving ExamSOA GI - Financial and Regulatory EnvironmentSOA GI - Advanced Topics in General InsuranceFSA ModulesFSA Module - Advanced Topics in CFEFSA Module - Financial EconomicsFSA Module - Financial ModelingFSA Module - Health FoundationsFSA Module - Social InsuranceFSA Module - Applications of Statistical Tech.FSA Module - Regulation & TaxationFSA Module - Health EconomicsFSA Module - Introduction to ILAFSA Module - Scenario ModelingFSA Module - Introduction to CFEDMAC - Decision Making and Communication Module EA ExamsEA-1EA2-FEA2-LCERA Designation for CASVEE Accounting and Finance (Corporate Finance)VEE EconomicsSOA Exam P / CAS Exam 1 SOA Exam FMSOA IFMCAS MAS-ICAS MAS-IICAS 5CAS 6CAS 7CAS 9SP9CERA Designation for SOAVEE EconomicsVEE Accounting and Finance (Corporate Finance)VEE Mathematical StatisticsSOA Exam P / CAS Exam 1 SOA Exam FMSOA IFMSOA STAMSOA SRMSOA ERM- General Corporate ERM Extension SOA ERM- General Insurance Extension SOA ERM- Group & Health Extension SOA ERM- Individual Life & Annuities Extension SOA ERM- Investment Extension SOA ERM- Retirement Benefits ExtensionVEE - Validation by Educational ExperienceVEE EconomicsVEE Accounting and Finance (Corporate Finance)VEE Mathematical StatisticsSeminars & Online CoursesSOA SeminarsCAS SeminarsVEE On Line CoursesPrerequisitesCalculusProfessional DevelopmentProfessional DevelopmentWebinars - ERMWebinars - Excel SkillsWebinars - HealthWebinars - IFRS & GAAPWebinars - InsurTechWebinars - Leadership & CommunicationWebinars - Predictive AnalyticsWebinars - Professionalism & EthicsWebinars - R & Python TrainingWebinars - AdditionalSOFE ExamsAFECFEOther ProductsCalculatorsActuarial Career AdvancementGift CertificatesOther
My Account
Modify My Account
My Learning Tools
Cust. Service
Build Your Own Study Program
Print Order Form
Track a Shipment
View Order History / Print Receipt
Privacy Policy
The Actuarial Bookstore takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy:
Our privacy policy covers the Actuarial Bookstore's treatment of personal information
that is collected when you are on the Actuarial Bookstore site, and when you purchase
any of our products or services. The Actuarial Bookstore uses this information for
only two purposes: customer service and to notify you directly about additional products
and services.
Email is our primary means of contacting you regarding customer service issues.
We may however, also use email to notify you of additional products, availability
of our new order form or other marketing purposes. You may restrict our marketing
solicitations by modifying your account information
or by sending an email to sales@actuarialbookstore.com.
Unless specifically necessary to complete your order, the Actuarial Bookstore will not share, sell or rent your personal information to any individual, company or organization whose textbooks, manuals or other study materials we offer for sale. For example, the sale of online courses does necessitate the release of your email address to the course provider.
However, the sale of a printed textbook or other printed study material (unless paired with an electronic component) does not allow for the release of your email or other contact information.
Similarly, we do not sell or rent your personal information to any 3rd party individuals, companies or organizations.
Your Actuarial Bookstore account information
is password-protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas of our website,
Actuarial Bookstore uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.
We utilize Google Analytics to collect and analyze cyber traffic data from our website. When someone visits our website, Google Analytics collects data from the visitor’s browser as well as first party cookies. The data extracted from the first party cookies includes site preferences as well as distinguishes unique visitors to our site. All collected data is anonymous by default.
We will not (and will not allow any third party to) use the service to track, collect, or upload any data that personally identifies an individual (such as names, email addresses, or billing information). The data is compiled into statistical reports by Google Analytics and is then shared exclusively with the Actuarial Bookstore. We make use of the following features of Google Analytic’s Display Advertising service: Remarketing, Network Impression Reporting, and Demographics and Interest Reporting.
We utilize the Remarketing feature offered by Google Analytics to target consumers who were in the process of checking out an item, but never completed the order process and in turn, “abandoned” their item in the online shopping cart. That consumer would then see Actuarial Bookstore ads appear on other Display Network websites and apps.
We utilize Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting feature, which gives us access to information that we can use to approximate our website visitors' demographics and interests. This information will be used to improve the usability of the site and deliver more relevant content to our customers.
Google offers website visitors the ability to prevent their data from being used by Google Analytics. You may download the feature here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
Please contact us if you have any questions or
concerns.
×
My Learning Tools Login
In order to access My Learning Tools, You must first be logged into our website. Clicking the Continue button will bring you to our login page. Once you have signed in, simply select the My Learning Tools option again, and your content will be displayed.
Continue
